

Julia Lima

UX Designer

Auckland, New Zealand **Phone:** +64 27 511 3958

Email: julia.lima.dg@gmail.com **Web Portfolio:** julialima.com.ar **LinkedIn:** linkedin.com/in/limajulia

Reliable, well-organized, professional and constantly seeking to improve. UX designer with two years of experience in a software company. Excellent at solving problems creatively and quickly. Interested in growing as a person and as a professional permanently, looking for permanent feedback.

Skills & Tools

Ideation
Wireframing
User Research
Visual Design
Interaction Design
Responsive Design
Documentation

Sketch (Wireframing)
InVision (Prototyping)
CSS/HTML (Web Development &
Prototyping)
Typeform (User Research)
Heap (Data Analysis)

Education & Certifications

BACHELOR IN DESIGN - MINOR: GRAPHIC Universidad Provincial de Córdoba Argentina

DEVELOPMENT AND DESIGN OF WEB PAGES Universidad Tecnológica Nacional Córdoba - Argentina

USER RESEARCH - METHODS AND BEST PRACTICES Interaction Design Foundation Online course

USER EXPERIENCE DESIGN ACCELERATE Academy Xi Melbourne - Australia

Work Experience

FERGUS SOFTWARE LTD.

Position: UX Designer. Jan 2018 - Present. Auckland, New Zealand

- Helping to improve a job management software for trades businesses from a user experience perspective
- Defining/improving interactions
- Providing wireframes and prototypes
- Actively collaborating with PM, PA and Developers
- Detailed design reviews
- User feedback analysis
- Ideating new features (web and mobile)
- Documenting behaviours and design patterns
- Conducting usability testing sessions

GRUPO PROYECTAR

Position: Product Designer - Freelance & Co-founder. Aug 2017 - Present. Argentina & remote

- Close collaboration with stakeholders
- Designed the interaction of both web and mobile apps
- Permanent contact with developers
- Current usage: ~1000 users

TURÍSTICOS

Position: Product Designer - Freelance and Co-founder. 2016 - 2018. Argentina & remote

- Designed an ecommerce website for the tourism industry
- Close collaboration with a Tourism Expert and Developer
- Definition of interactions and visual style
- Current usage: 200 users in two cities in Argentina

GNOME OUTREACH PROGRAM FOR WOMAN

Position: UI Designer - Intern. Dec 2014 - Feb 2015. Remote

- Defined and documented design principles, page layout and structure, UI elements and visual design
- Close communication with a Library Programmer/Analyst to define requirements along the whole project